snap-raise.com 2019-03-27

# Snap! Raise • Privacy Policy

## We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. No user information will be sold or shared in any way to any third party website for any reason whatsoever. 

_**What information do we collect?**_

We collect information from you when you register on our site or place an order. 

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number or credit card information. You may, however, visit our site anonymously. 

_**What do we use your information for?**_

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways: 

  * To process transactions
  * To send periodic emails
  * Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the expressed purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested

The email address you provide for order processing will only be used to send you information and updates. No emails are sent without your authorization. 

_**How do we protect your information?**_

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or access your personal information. 

We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems and who are required to keep the information confidential. 

After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.) will not be stored on our servers. 

_**Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**_

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. No user information will be sold or shared in any way to any third party website for any reason whatsoever. 

There is basic information that you may transmit via third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you. This only applies to actions you take by utilizing the share functionality that post information, with your permission, on [www.facebook.com](http://www.facebook.com/) and www.twitter.com. No other information that is ever stored about you is shared with any third parties. 

**For Example:** if you choose to utilize the share functionality of the site to send messages via Facebook, you are governed by facebook’s privacy policy while completing actions on their website. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. 

_**Third party links**_

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites. This applies to any links that a user may click that redirects the user to another website. This is currently not utilized by [www.snap-raise.com in]() any way. 

_**Children's Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**_

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act). We do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older. 

_**Online Privacy Policy Only**_

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline. 

_**Terms and Conditions**_

Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website at [www.Snap-Raise.com](http://snap-raise.com/)

_**Your Consent**_

By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy. 

_**Changes to our Privacy Policy**_

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, and/or send an email notifying you of any changes. 

_**Contacting Us**_

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below. 

939 Westlake Ave N   
Seattle, WA, 98109   
USA   
206-455-8424
